GIFT MAPOSA

GAME DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Johannesburg, 2194 South Africa

PHONE

0677492380

EMAIL

maposagift4@gmail.com

LINKS

LinkedIn

SKILLS

Fast Learner

Communication

Ability to Work in a Team

Analytical Thinking

Programming

Unity Game Engine

Source Control

C# Programming

HOBBIES

My passions include playing competitive gaming. I enjoy dabbling in a variety of games to widen my scope of knowledge. I'm currently learning how to play the Guitar. I enjoy listening to a variety of music and watching anime, shows and sports.

PROFILE

Currently working on Khamani: The Lion of Summer in association with Itthynk Gaming as the Lead Game Developer in the project. I lead the team in implementing systems, animations, assets etc. I specialize in Unity Development. My goals for this project are to further improve on my systems development skills and to be an overall better Unity developer.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Game Developer, Itthynk Gaming

Randburg

Mar 2023 — Present

 I'm a Game Developer at Itthynk Gaming, currently working on Khamani: The Lion of Summer. I'm the lead programmer on this project. My goal for this project is to further improve my Game Development skills while creating a fully fledged PC game using the Unity engine.

Game Developer, Atrybute Graphics

Johannesburg

Mar 2022 — Present

- I'm a Game Developer at Atrybute Graphics, working on multiple projects for the company.
- With Atrybute Graphics I helped develop and Release Fatpack Joe through the Incubation programme at Tshimologong Precinct.

Game Developer, Tshimologong Precinct

Johannesburg

Mar 2022 — Mar 2023

 I was in a gaming incubation with a team to further improve our development skills in the gaming industry. During this time we developed the game Fatpack Joe that was released on the Android Play Store.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering Science in Digital Arts, University of the Witwatersrand

Johannesburg

Feb 2017 — Dec 2020

• I studied towards a joint degree in Game Design and Electrical engineering. Through it, I have gained an

understanding of technical subjects such as Engineering Design, Electronics, Mathematics, Physics, and

Programming. I also have gained skillsets in Game design and game development accompanied by my

programming background.

National Senior Certificate, Trinity Secondary School

Lenasia

Jan 2012 — Dec 2016

- · Final Overall average: 72%
- Subjects: English (Home Language), Afrikaans (First Additional Language), Mathematics, Life Science,

Physical Science, Economics, Life Orientation

REFERENCES

Tyrene Homolang Marule from Atrybute Graphics

tyrenemarule@gmail.com

PROJECTS

Fatpack Joe

Johannesburg

Mar 2022 — Oct 2023

- Fatpack Joe is a humorous game about a kid who makes a jet-pack out of a couch, tape and a pair of missiles. The player is challenged to control this monstrosity to stop an alien invasion in single player or against other players in multiplayer. The invasion leads Joe on an adventure from Earth to other planets, realms and galaxies. The game is a unique spin on Afro-futurism: mixing elements of African art and the solar-punk aesthetic.
- · The game is available on the Google Play Store.